Guide to the Golf records, 1933-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Golf records 1933-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. Sports Information Office.
9.8 Linear Feet 9,700 Items
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches.
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the men and women's golf team at Duke University. The material ranges in date from 1933-ongoing.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Golf records were received by the University Archives as a transfer over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the SI Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the men and women's golf team at Duke University. The material dates from 1933-ongoing.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University. Sports Information Office
Duke University -- Golf -- History -- 20th century
Duke University -- Sports
Related Material
Athletic Dept. Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Scrapbooks.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photographic Negative Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Chanticleer Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletic Council Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletics Reference Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Yearly Files, 1933-2001, 13 Boxes
  The Yearly files contain clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, and tournament programs concerning the golf team at Duke University.
  - Men's Golf, 1933-2001
  - 1933-1962 (Box 1)
  - 1962-1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981-1987 (Box 3)
  - 1987-1992 (Box 4)
  - 1993-1996 (Box 5)
  - 1996-2000 (Box 6)
  - 2000-2001 (Box 14)
  - Women's Golf, 1968-2001
  - 1968-1984 (Box 7)
  - 1984-1992 (Box 8)
  - 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - 1994-1998 (Box 10)
  - 1998-2000 (Box 11)
  - 2000-2001 (Box 13)
- Media Guides, 1974-ongoing, 1 Box
  - Men's Golf, 1980-1993 c.1 (Box 12)
  - Men's Golf, 1999-2006 c.1
  - Men's Golf, c.2 various dates
  - Women's Golf, 1974-1997 c.1
  - Women's Golf, 1997-2002 c.1
  - Women's Golf, 2002-2008 c.1
  - Women's Golf, c.2 various dates